=Demon Emperor's Little Matchmaker=
= صانع الثقاب الصغير للإمبراطور الشيطاني =
=Episode 28=
= الحلقة 28 =
Young Master, I'm very happy for you today.
السيد الشاب ، أنا سعيد جدًا من أجلك اليوم.
When we arrive at Demon Emperor's Hall,
عندما وصلنا إلى قاعة إمبراطور الشيطان ،
you can succeed to the throne of Demon Emperor
يمكنك أن تجلس على عرش الإمبراطور الشيطاني
and restore your family glory.
واستعادة مجد عائلتك.
The previous Demon Emperor
الإمبراطور الشيطاني السابق
can finally rest in peace.
يمكن أخيرًا أن يرقد بسلام.
All thanks to Chuchu.
كل الشكر لـ Chuchu.
Yes. Ms. Chuchu was a great help.
نعم.  السيدة تشوتشو كانت مساعدة كبيرة.
Oh no, something bad happened to Chuchu.
أوه لا ، حدث شيء سيء لـ Chuchu.
The protection amulet I gave her has disappeared.
اختفت تميمة الحماية التي قدمتها لها.
Chuchu.
حلمات.
You're fast.
أنت سريع.
You must have rushed back before the ritual is done.
يجب أن تكون قد هرعت إلى الوراء قبل انتهاء الطقوس.
Demon Prince.
أمير شيطان.
Indeed.
في الواقع.
Congratulations on succeeding to the throne.
مبروك على تولي العرش.
Don't do anything to me.
لا تفعل أي شيء بي.
Or else it'll be the empress who gets injured.
وإلا ستكون الإمبراطورة هي التي تصاب.
What do you want? Where's Chuchu?
ماذا تريد؟  أين تشوتشو؟
As long as you give up the Soul-setting Pearl
طالما أنك تتخلى عن لؤلؤة الروح
and your demonic power,
وقوتك الشيطانية ،
I'll return you
سأعود لك
your unharmed beauty.
جمالك سالم.
Wuyou, don't trust her.
Wuyou ، لا تثق بها.
This must be a scheme.
يجب أن يكون هذا مخطط.
Wuming.
ويومينغ.
Okay.
تمام.
Provided that
بشرط
I can see Chuchu first.
أستطيع أن أرى تشوتشو أولاً.
Okay. You're frank.
تمام.  أنت صريح.
As long as you behave,
ما دمت تتصرف ،
after Li Wuyou agrees to our conditions,
بعد موافقة Li Wuyou على شروطنا ،
I'll let you go.
سأدعك تذهب.
What conditions?
ما هي الشروط؟
They're of course...
إنهم بالطبع ...
You don't need to know this.
لا تحتاج إلى معرفة هذا.
I think
أظن
Demon Prince didn't even tell you about it.
لم يخبرك Demon Prince حتى عن ذلك.
Perhaps he has always wanted to get a new subordinate.
ربما كان يريد دائمًا الحصول على مرؤوس جديد.
A more helpful assistant.
مساعد أكثر إفادة.
Nonsense!
كلام فارغ!
Really?
هل حقا؟
Does he always scold you or even beat you up?
هل يوبخك دائمًا أو حتى يضربك؟
He...
هو...
In this world,
في هذا العالم،
why does everyone
لماذا يفعل الجميع
look down upon me?
ينظر إلي بازدراء؟
What did I do wrong?
أي خطأ ارتكبت؟
Who did I offend?
من أساءت؟
Okay, stop.
حسنًا ، توقف.
What did I do wrong?
أي خطأ ارتكبت؟
Stop.
قف.
It was unnecessary.
كان غير ضروري.
Actually after awhile,
في الواقع بعد فترة ،
you look
أنت تبدو
quite unique.
فريد من نوعه.
It takes time to appreciate beauty.
يستغرق الأمر وقتًا لتقدير الجمال.
Well,
نحن سوف،
Demon Prince told me not to kill you.
أخبرني أمير الشيطان ألا يقتلك.
But he didn't say that I can't cut your face.
لكنه لم يقل أنني لا أستطيع قطع وجهك.
I want to torture you slowly.
أريد أن أعذبك ببطء.
Cut your face
اقطع وجهك
so you become ugly.
حتى تصبح قبيحا.
Let's see if Li Wuyou still wants you.
دعنا نرى ما إذا كان Li Wuyou لا يزال يريدك.
♪The wind of the early summer♪
رياح أوائل الصيف ♪
♪Created a starry sky♪
♪ خلق السماء المرصعة بالنجوم
♪The dream in my heart♪
الحلم في قلبي ♪
♪Froze at the street intersection in the morning♪
تجمد عند تقاطع الشارع صباحا
♪I've passed the end of the galaxy♪
♪ لقد اجتزت نهاية المجرة
♪I've seen the crowded traffic♪
♪ لقد رأيت ازدحام المرور ♪
♪In my mind♪
♪ في ذهني ♪
♪Your smile is engraved♪
♪ ابتسامتك محفورة ♪